pornseller.com 2011-06-18

# Adult DVD Empire -

Your privacy is important to Right Ascension, Inc. ("DVD Empire"). We realize that visiting adultdvdempire.com (the “Website”) requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly and pledge to you, our customer, that we will work to protect the security and privacy of your personal information. 

We believe that you have a right to know the personal information that we collect from you, why we collect it and how we use the information. This Privacy Policy covers how we collect, use, disclose, store and protect your personal information. 

Read More About:   
1\. Personal information collected  
2\. Use of your personal information  
3\. With whom we share your personal information  
4\. How you can control the use of your personal information  
5\. How you can decide what marketing communication you receive from us  
6\. How we protect the security of your personal information  
7\. Changes to the Privacy Policy  
8\. How to contact DVD Empire

**1\. Personal information collected**

We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using the Website. This information includes your name, email address and a password when you create your Empire Account. While you can browse our online store without opening an account, you will need to create an account in order to make purchases and take advantage of certain features. We may also ask for personal information when you contact our Help Desk. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity. 

The Website contains sexually-oriented adult material and they are not intended for individuals under 18 years of age. DVD Empire does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from individuals under 18 years of age who visit the Website. If a person under 18 years of age has provided DVD Empire with personally identifiable information, we ask that a parent or guardian immediately contact Customer Service for assistance. 

_Purchase Information_

When you make a purchase using a credit card, we collect your name and billing address for the card, the card type, number, and expiration date. We collect this information in order to verify your billing address. We also collect information that allows us to ship your purchase and keep you informed of the status of your order. This includes your email address and the name, address, and telephone number of the intended recipient(s). Billing information may also be provided over the phone by calling DVD Empire at 1-724-772-6030. 

If you created an Empire Account, you can choose to save your billing information for one or more credit cards in "Your Account". You may change or delete this saved information anytime. Simply go to Your Account, log-in with your username and password and edit whatever personal information you wish. 

_Cookies and other computer information_

When you visit the Website, you will be assigned a "cookie" (a small, unique identifier text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit the Website so that we can enhance and customize your online shopping experience. 

You can choose to shop on the Website without cookies, but without these identifier files you will not be able to take advantage of certain features of our site. These features include remembering your password (so you don't have to log in each time you visit), storing your Order for later use and, in the future, providing a more personalized shopping experience. To shop without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) 

We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you visit a page on the Website. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring website, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to our site. 

_Other times we may collect personal information_

If you ask for an Adult DVD Empire catalog, DVD Empire collects your name, mailing address, and date of birth when you complete the catalog Request. At the time you request a catalog, you may also choose to opt-out of receiving occasional offers from other quality companies that complement the Adult DVD Empire lifestyle. If you choose to opt-out, your name, mailing address and date of birth will not be shared with those other companies. When you make a purchase from an Adult DVD Empire catalog (including mail, fax and phone orders, the online catalog quick order form, and the online interactive version of the catalog) you are automatically opted-in to receive offers from other companies that complement the Adult DVD Empire lifestyle. You may opt-out of receiving the Adult DVD Empire catalog and from receiving offers from other companies, at any time, by requesting removal from the mailing lists here. 

From time to time, DVD Empire may conduct surveys and contests via our Website, email, or other forms of media. If you choose to participate, we may request your name, email address, mailing address and other personal information. We will use your email address to respond to your questions, suggestions, and/or requests for assistance in using our site. 

[Back to Top]

**2\. Use of your personal information**

Information we collect on the Website may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways: 

  * Deliver merchandise that you purchase online 
  * Register you as a member of DVD Empire 
  * Bill your credit card for your purchases 
  * Confirm your shopping orders 
  * Respond to your customer service inquiries or requests 
  * Notify you about sales and specials, as well as offers that compliment your shopping experience, unless you choose to opt-out of such communications 
  * Find and stock the products you want 
  * Customize your shopping experience 

[Back to Top]

**3\. With whom we share your personal information**

We never sell or rent your email address to unaffiliated companies. We may use your email address to send you messages that describe new items, sales, specials and other offers that we think will be of interest to you. If you would like to opt-out of receiving these emails from DVD Empire or its affiliates, please click on Your Account, log-in, go to Account Section, and follow the instructions outlined in the Notification Options section. 

We also do not sell other personal customer information to unaffiliated third-parties. We will share personal customer information that we collect only with DVD Empire affiliates, agents, representatives and trusted service providers for the limited purposes of fulfilling customer orders; offering certain products and services in connection with the Website; offering products or services which we believe you may be interested; communicating to customers; providing customer service; enhancing and improving the customer shopping experience; and providing a personalized shopping experience and completing credit card transactions. We may use or share with our strategic partners and affiliates, aggregated demographic and statistical information. This information is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. DVD Empire may assign or transfer any or all of your personal information to the relevant third-party in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale of the assets of DVD Empire. 

Aside from the purposes described above, we may also disclose your personal information in special circumstances if required to do so by law, court order or other governmental authority or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of DVD Empire, another user or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. 

[Back to Top]

**4\. How you can control the use of your personal information**

Creating a DVD Empire account lets us provide a better shopping experience for you and allows you to make purchases more conveniently without having to re-enter your payment and shipping information each time you make a purchase on our site. Although you must create an Empire Account in order to purchase DVD Empire products, it is not necessary to open an account to visit our site. 

As an existing customer, you can modify your personal information anytime. Simply go to Your Account, log-in with your username and password, then click "Contact Information" and edit whatever information you wish. To have your personal information deleted, contact our Customer Service Department by telephone at 1-724-772-6030 for further details. 

Do not share your password with anyone. Other than requested on the Website, DVD Empire will never ask you for your password. 

[Back to Top]

**5\. How you can decide what marketing communication you receive from us**

We may periodically send you email messages describing new items, sales, specials and other offers that we think will be of interest to you. If you would like to opt-out of receiving these emails from dvdempire.com, please click on Your Account, log-in, go to “Account Section”, click on “Notification Options” and remove the check in the box next to the “Sales & Specials” notification option. You can also opt-out of receiving these messages by clicking the ‘Unsubscribe” link in the email message itself. 

The only email messages you will receive from DVD Empire when you elect not to receive informational emails will be to confirm any purchases you make on our site, let you know your order has been shipped, respond to your Help Desk inquiries and to answer any other questions you may have about our site. We may also need to send operational emails to inform you of any changes to our site that might affect your personal information, or to announce product recalls. 

[Back to Top]

**6\. How we protect the security of your personal information**

The security of your personal information is very important to us. In our efforts to protect your online transactions, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL (and most are), your personal information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet. 

DVD Empire has also obtained a digital certificate from DigiCert®, a leading provider of Internet trust services. When you enter a secure portion of our site (which is any page containing any of your personal information), an image of a closed lock or a solid key should appear in the bottom bar of your browser window. If you click on this image, a small pop-up window displaying site-security information will appear. This certificate guarantees that your personal information is being transmitted in secure (encrypted) form to a DVD Empire Web server, not to some unknown or unauthorized server. 

Ultimately, your personal information is protected by the password that you entered when you created an Empire Account (or another password you chose after changing a previous password). Please keep this password confidential. The confidentiality of your password is your responsibility to protect. You may change it anytime by going to Your Account. Log in with your username and password, then click "Change Password" and enter a new password. 

[Back to Top]

**7\. Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice, and we encourage you to check this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy and your continued use of the Website constitutes your agreement as to all such updated or modified Privacy Policies. By using or visiting the Website, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy, then do not use or visit the Website.  [Back to Top]

**8\. How to contact DVD Empire**

If you have comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please Email Us. We will address any issue to the best of our abilities. 

Thank you for your support of our policies.  [Back to Top]

Last updated: May 3, 2011
